It's going to be a long night.
Security is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Alain Desrochers.
An ex-special services veteran, down on his luck and desperate for work, takes a
job as a security guard at a run-down mall in a rough area of town.
On his first night on the job, he opens the door to a distraught and desperate young girl who has fled the
hijacking of a Police motorcade that was transporting her to testify as a witness in a trial.
Hot on her heels is the psychopathic hijacker and his team of henchmen, who
will stop at nothing to extract and eliminate the witness.
Eduardo 'Eddie' Deacon, played by Antonio Banderas.
Charlie, played by Ben Kingsley.
Vance, played by Liam McIntyre.
Mason, played by Chad Lindberg.
Ruby, played by Gabriella Wright.
Dead Eyes, played by Cung Le.
Security is a 2017 American action thriller film directed by Alain
DesRochers and written by Tony Mosher and John Sullivan.
The film stars Antonio Banderas, Gabriella Wright,
Ben Kingsley, and Chad Lindberg.
The film explores themes of shopping mall, security guard, witness elimination.
The tone is intense.